Justin Choi

Edmonton, AB (780)-200-3020 justin.choi.000@gmail.com

Web developer with over 10 years of experience dealing with both front-end and back-end projects. Ruby on Rails-focused career with strong TDD background. Also experienced with JS frameworks such as Backbone.js.

Professional Experience

Atlas Web Development (May 2013 - November 2016)

- Performed a Rails 2 to Rails 4 code upgrade.
- Dealt with online payment gems.
- Installed process-monitoring daemons to prevent downtime of business sites.
- Extended functionality of CMS to include broader file types, from plain text articles to videos.
- Developed back-end processing which handled data from a related mobile app which was then displayed on a heat map along with other statistics.

Popper (January 2013 - April 2013)

- Integrated existing software to a web interface.
- Performed calculations via software external to the web server and displayed results on the website.
- Performed application-wide fixes following a database switch which killed all functionality.
- Observed NDA.

Education

University of Alberta

Computer Science 2011 - 2014

Additional Skills

- Accomplished in collaborative work while in a leadership position due to time served as an administrator on a public wiki.
- Experienced in public relations and arbitration from position as moderator for WF Recruitment School Bus, previously known as Warframe Raid School Bus (WFRSB).
- Steadfast mindset in the face of a stiff challenge. Originally born from gaming, this trait has extended to many other faucets.